Hello ?
- Sorry .
Can you let me in ?
- Hi . - Hey .
You ready for tonight ?
Yeah . Yeah , it should be fun .
Um . Have you ever done anything like this before ?
- No . - No ?
Yeah , it 's ... I 've done it a few times ,
and it is really cool . Like ...
Does anything ever happen ?
Yeah . Yeah .
I mean , every time I 've done it , it 's been - -
like , something has gone on .
Sounds spooky .
It 'll just be a little different .
Oh , she 's back . Yay .
Are we just waiting for the other guys ?
Yeah . Caroline just messaged me
and said she was running a little bit late .
Okay . There we go .
I think you needed to ...
turn off the phone audio .
You got to turn off the phone audio , I think .
Maybe mute - - mute yourself on one , or ...
Okay .
Yeah .
That 's good .
There she is .
Sorry , do you mind if I just send a really quick e-mail ?
Yeah , no , no .
Go for it .
Yeah .
- Hi , guys . - Hello . - Hi .
How are you ? Good . How are you ?
I 'm nervous .
What 's there to be nervous about ?
It 's gonna be fine . It 's gonna be fun .
- Hey , guys . - Radina !
Hi ! How are you ?
- Radina . - Oh , my God .
Your hair 's so lovely and curly like that .
- Thank you . - Hello , girl .
Hello .
Oh , is it something ?
She 's coughing .
I 'm fine , guys .
People are not allowed to cough anymore .
This is ridiculous .
Well , you have to hide a cough with a fart now
instead of the other way around .
That 's true .
Tuck it in .
- Oh , Caroline ! - What ?
Caroline !
Caroline , there 's something on your face .
My pores are not doing well in lockdown , so ...
Hello .
- Hi , Pat ! - Hi , Pat .
Did you ask if he 's staying indoors ?
No , he 's not staying indoors , are you ?
No , no , no , no , no . I like the sunshine .
Oh , Pat , you 've got to be careful .
I absolutely love it .
Oh , my God . Put it away .
- You 're such a flirt ! - Oh , my God !
Bye , Dad .
I love your dad .
You should invite him tonight .
I don 't think his heart could handle it .
He 's so cute . He 's been so naughty , though .
Just keeps going out , and then I have to - -
I have to , like , chase him down the street ,
and I 'm like , " Dad , stop it ! "
Just excuse me for one second .
Is she okay ?
Yeah , she 's alright .
It doesn 't look alright .
It 's a weird situation , isn 't it ?
Well , they should have never moved in together for lockdown .
Yeah , you don 't know a person in that short of time .
Well , what do you know ?
Radina . Hey .
Hey .
You okay ? Yeah .
Oh , my God , yeah . Totally fine .
It 's like , when we have an argument ,
he just goes to the bedroom .
Now I have all this space .
Hey , guys . Look at this .
This is gonna be us later .
Emma . Not funny .
I don 't like that .
It 's gonna appear behind you , Caroline .
Oh , shut up .
- Emma . - Wait .
Wait , look what I did . Hang on .
It takes a while .
This is what lockdown 's led me to .
Look , look . It 's me .
- Oh , my God ! - Got a twin .
- Oh , no . - There 's two of you .
Yeah , no . I got lonely , so I made a friend .
Oh , my God , guys , I heard from Teddy .
He 's actually gonna be there tonight .
Oh , he is ? Hang on . Are you serious ?
Thought I 'd give you the heads up , Caroline .
Yeah , thanks for that . A bit late .
Got this shit on my face .
Have you seen his Instagram posts ?
The one with Ginny or the other one with Ginny ?
Or the first one with Ginny ?
Her parents ' house is , like , a mansion .
He 's so different now . Like ...
Well , it 's her . She 's so fucking painful , guys .
You 'd never put them together , ' cause Teddy is the opposite .
Well , you can have , like , three conversations
with her in rotation and that 's about it .
And I 've definitely seen her , like , fake tan hand marks .
Like - - Hi , Teddy !
- Hi , Teddy ! - Hi !
- Hey . - Hey , buddy .
- Hey . - Hi , Ginny .
- How you doing , guys ? - Hey , Ginny .
You made it . How 's it going ?
Gin and tonic there .
You 're fancy now .
Quarantine has really done you good .
Oh , it 's delish . Hang on .
I 'll come inside . The signal 's ...
Yes . Just living the life by the pool .
- Oh , no . - Oh , come on .
- Bye , Ginny ! - Bye !
Oh , my God .
You coming on your own , Ted ?
Yes . Big boy stuff .
I 'm all by myself with you lot .
You got a little man-bun going .
When did you get a man-bun ?
I think it 's a twat knot from corona .
Shall I give you a little tour around ?
Yes , please . Hang on .
Check this guy out .
- Very creepy . - So creepy .
Yeah , what the fuck ?
You literally have no fucking idea
how close this thing is . Yeah , let 's check out the ...
Is that a bar behind you ?
Yes . Yeah , it is .
The fucking hardest thing is not getting cunted
in front of her dad . There 's so much booze here ,
and yes , it 's not exactly like I can bring out
Red Ted from the ' 99 days .
Oh , Red Ted .
But it 's weird being with her and her parents .
They 've got these weird rules , like - -
like , no Pornhub in the dining room , and ...
How are you surviving ? Barely .
Barely . I 'm a man on the edge .
I 'm a man on the edge .
Ted , how are you feeling about tonight ?
Do you have your item ? I do .
Yeah , yeah , I 've got it .
Bro , this is how seriously I 'm taking this fucking thing .
I went home to - - I broke quarantine
to go and get this , so ...
You ? I 'm telling .
I 'll make this as atmospheric as I can .
Wow . Oh , my God .
Fuckin ' creepy . You hear it ?
Yeah . Yes .
So , basically , it was - - it 's my nan 's , but I fucking - -
I literally fucking hate this , ' cause my brother - -
he used to be a right little shit .
He 'd go and hide it around the house ,
and it used to scare the shit out of me .
I genuinely used to cry .
To be honest , when I hear that music , it 's
It 's fuckin ' horrible .
It 's horrible . So , this - - this is his .
God bless him . If it 's playing , watch out .
That is so creepy . Sorry . That is ...
Are you not looking forward to it ?
I 'm a bit nervous .
I 'm absolutely shitting here .
Why ?
I really don 't want to do it .
It 'll be fine .
The woman is a friend of mine ,
so she 's done it a bunch of times for me .
She 'll kind of guide everybody through it .
You kind of just have to follow her instructions .
Just , please , she is a friend of mine .
Not that I don 't think you would ,
but please take it seriously , though ,
and be respectful .
Speaking of seriously ,
and not to undermine everything you 've just said ,
but can we do a ... cheeky little shot
every time she says " astroplane " .
Yes ! It 's my game !
Astral plane .
Astral plane . Not " astro " .
" Astral " .Vodka bottle right here .
Just don 't let her see .
I don 't know if she 'll be o - - like , cool with that .
Oh , while you guys are killing your livers ,
I 'm gonna drink water . That 's just - -
if we 're gonna do the shots , do it slightly ...
I mean , I can 't really do that with a beer .
Alright , let 's ... let 's do a shot guys .
To us . It 's fuckin ' nice to see you .
Here , take a picture .
Brought this guy back out .
What should we toast to ?
A ...
a happy - - happy seance ?
Yeah . Happy spookies .
Happy spookies .
Okay , everyone , get in .
Three , two , one .
Cheers . Cheers .
Cheers , guys .
Oh , she just texted me .
What 's it called when you , like , send something - -
something ? Telepathy .
Did she text you with telepathy ?
Tele - - Telethapy ?
So , she actually texted me .
With the phone . What 's she saying ?
She 's in the waiting room .
Scared !
Why are you making me do this ?
Can 't we just do , like , I don 't know .
A board game or something ?
Nothing 's gonna happen .
Exactly !
Oh , Teddy !
Teddy , keep that shut , please .
Alright , I 'm gonna let her in . Everybody ready ?
- Yes . - No .
Let 's do this .
I 'm joking .
Please . Remember , be respectful , everybody .
I 'm gonna let her into the room .
Hi , Seylan .
Hi . Can you hear me ?
- Yeah . - Hi .
Hi , Haley . How are you doing ?
Hi , everybody . Nice to meet you .
Nice to meet you , too .
Thanks so much for inviting me along .
I 've got to confess - -
I 've never done this before over Zoom .
So , it 's gonna be new for all of us , which should be fun .
Now , did Haley mention to you about trigger objects ?
That 's something you might have ,
that 's closely connected with somebody
that you might want to speak to this evening .
- You 've all got something ? - Yeah .
- Good . - Yep . - Can I ask - - Sorry .
Can I ask a question ? If my pa - -
my grandparents are Chinese and I am English
and I don 't speak Chinese , does that mean
that I will not be able to communicate with them ?
No . Not at all .
There 's no language on the astral plane ,
so if they want to communicate with you ,
then they will let you understand .
Okay . This might sound really silly ,
but can I potentially contact a dead pet ?
Yeah . Absolutely .
Like I said , on the astral plane , there 's no language .
If you bear in mind that the laws are different
from what they are here ,
so you might be able to talk to a pet .
Yeah , absolutely . Can we light these now ?
Yes . Go ahead and light your candles .
Yep . The candle is going to be our guiding focus
and it 's going to encourage the spirit .
It will give them almost a beacon to come towards .
So , what I want you to look out for
are the kind of response that you might get from spirit ,
and it might be a name or a face ,
an image that comes into your mind ,
but it can also be physical things ,
like you might hear a knock
or you might see your candle light flicker .
You could feel a touch , feel pressure on your body somewhere .
That 's the kind of thing that I want you to look out for .
Very quickly , before we start , what was the name of that plane ?
The astral plane .
Oh , right , right .
So , because we 're doing this over Zoom ,
what it does mean is that we 're slightly less
protected than we might have been ,
so it 's very important that you respect the spirits
and you respect each other .
Is anybody feeling worried ?
Does anybody ...
anybody feeling a bit vulnerable ?
Yeah , Emma and Caroline . Okay .
So , let me just quickly talk you through a process
that you can do any time ,
and normally , we would be in a circle , holding hands ,
with one candle in the center .
Because we 're all ...
not in the same place ,
we 're going to visualize the circle .
We 're going to visualize ourselves
breaking that circle ,
and then as an extra precaution ,
I 'd like you to visualize a cord or a rope around your waist
that 's leading towards your front door ,
and then visualize yourself cutting with
a knife or scissors , whatever you like .
Just make a real for yourself ,
and that will sever the connection
with the spirit realm .
Okay . Um , I 'm gonna switch on some isochronic tones ,
and they just help our energy
to join the vibrations of the spirit realm .
Okay . Now , close your eyes .
And I 'd like you just to visualize that circle .
Holy shit ! What are you doing ?
Knock it off , you shit .
Sorry , girls .
Hey .
What ?
Teddy .
- Ted . - Sorry , Ted 's got to go .
Bye . Are you serious ?
- Wow . - Did he just leave ?
Such a fucking knobsack . She 's a bitch .
In the span of like two minutes .
Listen , d-don 't worry .
Let 's not let this affect us .
Let 's just maintain our focus .
Um , obviously , we 're not here physically together ,
but there 's no reason why spirit can 't communicate with us
over the Internet .
Over the channel of communication ,
we could all be possessed .
Now - - - Possessed ?
Don 't be scared by that word .
That just means that the spirit is communicating through us .
It 's called " possessed " , but that doesn 't
have to be a negative thing . Just bear that in mind .
Now , I 'd like you , please , to visualize a circle .
Visualize us all together in the one room ,
sitting in a circle ,
and we 're just going to gently join hands with each other .
Spirit , we invite you to use us to pass
on any communication you might have .
Is there anyone there ? Please come forward .
And all together .
Okay .
Now , I want you to tell me if anything comes into your mind .
Perhaps a name , a face .
If you hear any sounds .
Radina , I don 't want to make you nervous , but ...
can anybody something going on just behind .
Yeah , looks like a light moving about .
Yeah . But I 'm kind of noticing something in between .
Probably just a reflection of something .
There 's a light on my fridge .
It 's moving , though.No .
This - - This is something different .
It was a light that was static , and it 's now moving .
- It 's moving quite a lot . - Yeah .
- I don 't like it . - Oh , I think - -
Oh , hold on . Hold on .
I can make it a third eye .
Okay , it 's on her face now .
What was that ?
- Haley , was that you ? - It wasn 't .
I didn 't do anything .
Did it - - Did everybody hear that ?
I heard it . I heard something .
Okay , let 's just listen out .
Um , spirit , if you 're trying to give us a sign ,
please knock one more time .
Fuck .
Oh , I 'm so sorry . That must be my delivery .
I 'm really sorry . I 'll be back in a second .
What ? !
Oh , my God . I 'm sorry . " That 's my Ocado . "
" Sorry , my food delivery 's arrived . "
I 'm getting a noise .
I 'm getting aubergines
a jar of tahini .
Is anybody else getting something ?
No , I just hear my next-door neighbors .
- Is she coming back ? - Where is she ?
Her house is kind of creepy in the dark .
Seylan ?
We paying her , Haley ?
- Oh , there she is . - She 's back .
Hey , guys . I 'm really sorry .
Sorry , sorry , sorry , sorry .
It was supposed to arrive before our session ,
so sorry about that .
Can we get back to where we were ?
Yeah .
So , let 's just focus a little bit more .
Is anybody getting a name , perhaps ?
Did anybody see that ?
Okay , what just happened ?
I felt , like , a hand on my - - on my shoulder .
Jemma ?
- Jemma , are you okay ? - What was it ?
Oh , my God , oh , my God , oh , my God , oh , my God .
Something just touched my neck .
Jemma , do you want to come and talk to us ?
Just try asking some questions , Jemma .
Honestly , the pressure on my neck is almost unbearable .
Do you want to call out and ask who it is ?
Maybe a name might come into your head , or ...
Hello ?
Is there ...
Is there someone there ?
The name Jack 's come to mind .
Okay .
That 's good .
Do you know anyone called Jack who 's passed ?
Yeah .
A kid from school .
He was really nice to me one time .
I cracked my head open ...
and he , like , picked me up .
He hanged himself .
Listen , Jemma , I want you to - -
Where did Seylan go ?
It might just be a bad connection .
- You , Call her , Haley . - Yeah .
Jemma - - Jemma , you alright ?
You okay , Jemma ?
Oh , my God . What ?
You bitch . No .
- You didn 't . - Oh , no .
- Oh , my God . - Jemma .
Did you make that up ?
Jemma , you 're a psychopath .
Nothing was happening .
Jemma , I believed you .
I 'm so - - I 'm so sorry .
There was just nothing being said .
I actually thought you were gonna , like , die .
Have we heard from Seylan ?
Yeah , is she okay ? What happened ?
I didn 't even see what happened .
Her Internet went out . I 'm gonna pee .
Yeah . I might , too , actually .
I 'm gonna be smashed if we carry this on .
Some water .
Ready , Haley ? Yep .
Oh , wait .
I 'm sensing some ...
tension .
But - - A name 's just come to mind .
Haley .
Haley !
Fuck off , Jemma .
Haley just can 't have fun .
You 're not taking it seriously like I asked you to .
Oh , shut up . I 'm so bored of this .
Oh , my God .
Why do we have to do this tonight , guys ?
You know what , Jemma ? Nobody - -
H-Haley , what 's going on ?
Oh , fuck .
Haley ?
I think there 's something here .
Haley , stop fucking about , please .
I swear , it wasn 't - - Look .
I - - We have to keep going .
- No . - Please - -
We connected with something . We got to keep going .
We got to talk to it . I 'm gonna call out .
No . No.Is anybody here ?
Does anyone want to talk to me ?
Turn your lights off . Haley , honestly , if I die ,
I 'm actually gonna haunt you myself .
Just listen .
I heard something .
Turn your microphones up .
Should be under settings .
Is anybody here ?
I don 't like this .
What was that ?
I heard something .
That wasn 't in my house .
Caroline .
Caroline . You got to go check it out .
Don 't do that .
That 's a stupid idea .
There 's probably nothing there . It 's okay .
Dad ?
What is it ?
It 's probably nothing .
Be careful .
Caroline , take us up .
It 's okay .
Go on , Caroline . It 's okay .
It 'll be fine .
No . No .
What are you doing , Caroline ?
Caroline , what are you doing ?
It 's gonna be fine .
Go on , Caroline . It 's okay .
It 's okay . We 're here .
Film what you see .
Do you see anything ?
- What 's that thing ? - Nothing , it 's just focusing .
Nothing 's there . It 's fine .
Look , look .
- Caroline , go back . - What the fuck was that ?
- What the fuck was that ? - I don 't see anything .
Caroline , go down . Caroline .
Don 't freak out . Don 't freak out .
- What was it ? - What the fuck was that ?
I definitely just saw something .
You have to call Seylan . Call Seylan .
Yeah , yeah . Just calm down . Calm down .
I 'm gonna call her . I 'm gonna call her .
I 'm calling her .
Haley ? What are you doing ?
Haley . Haley .
Do you see that ?
No . What ?
I can 't see anything ?
It 's not in there .
Haley , what is it ?
It looked at me .
No .
What is that ?
What the fuck ?
What the fuck , guys ?
This is not funny anymore . Stop taking the piss .
Call Seylan .
It 's ringing , it 's ringing . It 's ringing .
Hello ? Seylan ?
H-Haley ?
Haley , is that you ? Yeah .
I 'm so sorry . I 'm so sorry .
My Internet - - it 's a bit of a - -
Sorry , I 've not been able to get it going .
How 's it going ? We 've had some - -
We 've had some interesting experiences .
We 've just - - Caroline 's just a bit scared ,
so we 're just hoping you can talk us through .
Okay . Yeah . No - - No problem .
I mean , it 's - - it 's - - it 's good
that you 've had an experience .
That 's what we 're here for . I 'm really sorry
that I 've not been there to go through it with you ,
but can the others hear me ? Yeah , they can hear you .
They can hear you . Oh , they can hear me . Okay .
Listen , guys , don 't worry .
So , just - - let 's just keep calm .
It 's probably just - -
just somebody trying to pass on a message .
Jemma , you were telling us about your friend , Jack .
So , it sounds pretty likely that it 's him .
Have you tried asking if it 's Jack ?
I don 't know . Jemma , have we tried asking if it 's Jack ?
Jemma !
Sorry .
Jack 's not real .
What 's going on ? Wait . Jack 's not real .
Jemma made him up .
Jack doesn 't - - Jack doesn 't e-exist or - -
or Jack does exist . She just didn 't hear him ?
No , Jack doesn 't exist at all .
Look , guys , I ...
I told you not to disrespect the spirits .
This - - This isn 't good . This is not good .
I mean , basically , if - - by inventing a-a person
that doesn 't exist , we 've basically
summoned a false spirit .
If you made this person up , you - - you basically created - -
Imagine , like , you created a mask ,
so now anything can come through and wear that mask .
We - - We don 't know what it might be .
So ... I mean , if we 're lucky , it 's just - -
it 's just another spirit .
But what if - - what if we 're not lucky , though ?
H-Haley , ask her what if we 're not lucky .
What if we 're not lucky , Seylan ?
I-It could be something ...
demonic .
Look , I mean , basically , Jemma has sent out
an invitation , an open invitation .
We need to shut this down .
We need to - - Like I said to you .
We need to thank the spirits and close it down ,
and don 't forget that - - visualizing that rope .
Okay ? So ,
spirit , please give us one knock for " yes "
and two knocks for " no " .
Let 's ask , " Do you have a message for us ? "
After three . So , one , two , three .
Do you have a message for us ?
My light just turned on .
Okay , Haley , that 's great .
Let 's - - Okay .
let 's try another question .
All together , let 's ask , " Are you a friend ? "
One , two , three .
Are you a friend ?
Seylan ? Are you there ?
What the fuck is going on ? !
Call her back . Call her back now .
Fuck . Fuck , she 's not picking up .
Okay . Okay .
What do we do ? What do we do ? What do we do ? What do we do ?
What do we do ? Just a second . I know what to do .
Okay , we just have to do the - - the rope thing and - -
and we have to be polite to the spirit - -
You don 't know what you 're doing ! Just shut up , Jemma !
Just shut the fuck up for one second !
Imagine a rope . Imagine the rope around your waist ,
rope around your waist .
Okay . I 'm sorry , spirit .
I 'm sorry if we confused you .
Just repeat after me . I 'm sorry if we confused you .
Sorry if we confused you .
Um , imagine the rope to your door ,
and then we 're just gonna cut the rope .
Okay ? Okay , imagine we 're cutting the rope .
Okay . I 'm gonna call out again .
Is there anyone here ?
And then , um , open your eyes and blow out the candles
and that 'll break the circle .
I blew my candle already out .
It 's okay . It 's okay .
Just remember , she said it was just to guide them there ,
so it 's okay .
Bless you .
What the fuck ?
That was ... It was exciting .
Oh , my God . I 'm so hot .
I-I smell so bad .
I 'm really sweaty .
Oh , my God .
Guys , what the fuck was that ?
- Oh , God . - Never again .
Radina , are you on the toilet ?
Maybe .
Panic wee .
Guys , I 'm not going anywhere alone after what just happened .
Shut up .
You okay , Caroline ?
Fuckin ' hell . That gave me a shock .
Guys , I 'm literally not going to sleep tonight now .
Crazy , guys . Fuckin ' hell .
Emma , your glass .
I swear to God . I didn 't do anything .
That was an expensive one .
Wait until Teddy hears about this .
He 's just sitting there eating his Chinese
and we 've nearly died .
Oh , my God . I can 't wait to tell Teddy .
He 's gonna be , like , all flustered .
He 'll come back and we 're just gonna be like ,
" Mate , you 've just missed a storm . "
Guys , did anybody see Allen leaving ?
He left his phone .
Where is ...
Radina , has he gone to the shop to do ...
Maybe he 's at his brother 's .
Here , give him a call .
Crap . I 've actually finished the whole bottle of wine .
Guys , I think I 'm gonna head ...
This has been ,
Emma , my darling .
Goodbye , my dear . I love you .
Goodbye . Farewell . So long .
See you later . Bye , Haley .
Bye , girls . See you next time .
Can you say goodbye to Radina for me , please ?
Yeah , I mean ,
maybe we should wait until she gets back .
Oh , no , I think I 'm gonna head .
I think I 'm gonna head .
Caroline ?
Bye !
Caroline !
Oh , there she is .
Caroline . Hey , dude .
Caroline . Has she got her audio on ?
Caroline ?
I think so . Yeah .
Hello , friend .
Oh , wait . Isn 't this her background ?
Oh , yeah . You 're right . Yeah .
I 'm gonna give her a call .
What was that ?
Caroline , can you hear us , babe ?
I think her laptop just fell .
Caroline ? I 'm - - I 'm gonna call her .
What ...
Emma ! Emma , turn the filters off .
Come on .
Emma .
Hi , it 's Caroline . Don 't leave me a message .
Send me a text like a normal person .
Emma .
Fuck .
What are you doing ?
Don 't .
Emma ? It 's fine . It 's fine .
Emma , it 's gone . Come on .
Emma ? Emma , get out .
Emma , get out of that there right now !
Emma , you need to get out of there right now !
Emma ! Emma , get out !
Emma ! What was that ?
Fuck . Fuck , fuck .
You okay ?
Emma ? Emma , you need to get out of there .
Emma . Emma .
No , no , don 't go back in there .
Get out !
Emma ! Emma ! Emma , Emma , Emma !
Emma ! Emma !
Emma , talk to us . Emma , talk to us .
Emma , talk to us .
Emma , what was that ?
Emma , Emma , Emma .
Emma . It 's okay .
It 's okay . We 're here , we 're here .
It 's gonna be okay . It 's gonna be okay .
Just get out .
You 're gonna get out of the house , okay ?
We 're gonna go . Haley ?
Yeah , we 're going . We 're all doing it .
Radina .
Radina . Radina , we got to get out of the house .
Radina ! Radina !
Radina , Radina , Radina .
Radina ! What ?
Allen ! Allen !
Oh , my God !
Fuck !
Run ! Run !
Caroline ?
Caroline .
I don 't understand what she said .
Caroline !
Oh , my God !
Help me !
No ! No !
I 'm gonna call Seylan .
Haley .
Haley ! No ! Stop it , Haley !
Haley , this is all your fault ! It 's not my fault !
This is your fucking - -
Shut up !
Stop ! I told you to be - -
Haley . Haley .
Haley . Shut up !
Haley .
Haley !
Hello ?
No .
Oh , my God . What are you doing , Jemma ?
Jemma , where are you going ?
Emma , I 'll be right back . No !
Listen to me . You 'll be fine . Jemma , what are you doing ?
Don 't go , please . Jemma , please don 't go .
Emma , you 'll be fine . Jemma !
Emma , you 'll be fine !
Please don 't go !
Teddy .
Did I get ya ?
Sorry I took so long , man .
It was longer than we thought .
Fuckin ' hell . You get a tattoo ?
Teddy , get out . Get out of your house .
Okay , now , where is everybody ?
Oh , come on , you lot .
Stop hiding , you fat bitches .
Come out . Teddy , please .
Oh , fuck off . You lot are taking the piss .
What 's happened . Come on . Tell me .
Teddy , get out . Hang on a sec .
It 's just a power cut . It happens literally
all the time in the country .
Right , here we go . You ready ?
We 're gonna die.VoilÃ . We 're be back in action .
Teddy , Teddy .
Oh , my ... Hang on .
I 've got to go find the old ,
What you call it ? The box .
Seylan was a interesting character .
Please .
Get out . Teddy , get out !
Don 't stop ! Don 't stop !
Ginny ! Fuckin ' hell .
Ginny !
No !
No ! Get out , please .
There 's someone there ! Please !
No ! No !
Teddy , get out !
You 're gonna die if you don 't listen to me .
Teddy , run .
I think it 's here .
Teddy ?
Can you hear that ?
Teddy .
Teddy , get out .
What the fuck ?
Teddy , wake up .
Teddy , get up ! Move !
Can you hear me ?
Teddy . Teddy , answer me !
Teddy !
No !
Teddy , wake up !
No .
No ! No .
Teddy .
Emma .
Haley ?
Fuck you !
Fuck .
Fuck , fuck , fuck .
Fuck ! Haley .
Haley !
We need to get out , Haley .
We need to leave .
Did you see anything ?